nine.com.au 2005-06-16

# ninemsn support

|  | | ninemsn Highlights Privacy Notice  
---  
Last updated: 28 July, 2004 |  |  | 

Scope 

This notice provides highlights of the full Privacy Policy. This notice and the full Privacy Policy apply to information you provide on the ninemsn Network and under MSN services provided through our site. 

---|---|---  
| 

  * When you register as a [ninemsn Member](http://membership.ninemsn.com.au/memberspage.asp) or for other services offered on the ninemsn Network (including MSN services), we’ll ask you to provide personal information. 
  * The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from MSN services provided through our site and other companies. 
  * We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalised experience. 

|  | 

  * To make choices about how we communicate with you, go to [My Offers](http://membership.ninemsn.com.au/interest.asp). 
  * To subscribe or unsubscribe to newsletters, go to [My Newsletters](http://membership.ninemsn.com.au/newslettersprofile.asp). 
  * To view and edit your personal information, go to [My Profile](http://membership.ninemsn.com.au/Personalprofile.asp). 

---|---|---  
| 

  * We use the information we collect to provide the services you have explicitly requested. Our services may include the display of personalised content and advertising. 
  * We use your information to send you: updates on new services; member-only offers from our carefully selected partners; email newsletters to which you have subscribed, and, new competitions. 
  * We will never share your information with a third party or allow it to send you direct communications about its products without your consent. 
  * In order to help provide our services, we occasionally provide information to other companies who work on our behalf. 

|  | 

**Important information**

  * ninemsn is operated as a joint venture between Microsoft Corporation and Publishing and Broadcasting Limited. Any information you provide under MSN services provided through the ninemsn site, such as Hotmail, Instant Messenger and Search, may be collected and used both by Microsoft, as described in the [MSN Privacy Statement](http://privacy.msn.com/), and by ninemsn, as described in our full Privacy Policy. 
  * The e-mail address and password you use to sign-in on the ninemsn Network can also be used to sign in to other sites that are part the Microsoft Passport Network. To learn more about the Passport Network, [read the Microsoft Passport Network Privacy Statement](http://www.passport.net/Consumer/PrivacyPolicy.asp?PPlcid=2057).   

---|---|---  
|  | 

**How to contact us**

For more information about our privacy practices, go to the full Privacy Policy on our website, or write to us at: 

The Privacy Officer   
ninemsn Pty Limited   
Level 7 Tower Building, Australia Square   
264 George Street   
Sydney NSW 2000 

Send us e-mail

|   
---|---|---
